<resources>
    <string name="app_name">A013 30 Days of Animals</string>
    <string name="app_name_2">30 Days of Animals</string>

    <string name="animal_name_1">Lion</string>
    <string name="animal_name_2">Elephant</string>
    <string name="animal_name_3">Hummingbird</string>
    <string name="animal_name_4">Cat</string>
    <string name="animal_name_5">Snow Leopard</string>
    <string name="animal_name_6">Tiger</string>
    <string name="animal_name_7">Rhinoceros</string>
    <string name="animal_name_8">Turtle</string>
    <string name="animal_name_9">Zebra</string>
    <string name="animal_name_10">Giraffe</string>

    <string name="animal_description_1">The lion (Panthera leo) is a large cat of the genus Panthera native to Africa and India. It has a muscular, broad-chested body; short, rounded head; round ears; and a hairy tuft at the end of its tail. It is sexually dimorphic; adult male lions are larger than females and have a prominent mane. It is a social species, forming groups called prides. A lion\'s pride consists of a few adult males, related females, and cubs. Groups of female lions usually hunt together, preying mostly on large ungulates. The lion is an apex and keystone predator; although some lions scavenge when opportunities occur and have been known to hunt humans, lions typically do not actively seek out and prey on humans.</string>
    <string name="animal_description_2">Elephants are the largest living land animals. Three living species are currently recognised: the African bush elephant (Loxodonta africana), the African forest elephant (L. cyclotis), and the Asian elephant (Elephas maximus). They are the only surviving members of the family Elephantidae and the order Proboscidea; extinct relatives include mammoths and mastodons. Distinctive features of elephants include a long proboscis called a trunk, tusks, large ear flaps, pillar-like legs, and tough but sensitive grey skin. The trunk is prehensile, bringing food and water to the mouth and grasping objects. Tusks, which are derived from the incisor teeth, serve both as weapons and as tools for moving objects and digging. The large ear flaps assist in maintaining a constant body temperature as well as in communication. African elephants have larger ears and concave backs, whereas Asian elephants have smaller ears and convex or level backs.</string>
    <string name="animal_description_3">The sparkling violetear (Colibri coruscans) is a species of hummingbird widespread in highlands of northern and western South America, including a large part of the Andes (from Argentina and northwards), the Venezuelan Coastal Range, and the Tepuis. It occurs in a wide range of semi-open habitats, even in gardens and parks within major cities such as Quito, and is often the most common species of hummingbird in its range. It is highly vocal and territorial.</string>
    <string name="animal_description_4">The cat (Felis catus), commonly referred to as the domestic cat or house cat, is the only domesticated species in the family Felidae. Recent advances in archaeology and genetics have shown that the domestication of the cat occurred in the Near East around 7500 BC. It is commonly kept as a house pet and farm cat, but also ranges freely as a feral cat avoiding human contact. It is valued by humans for companionship and its ability to kill vermin. Because of its retractable claws it is adapted to killing small prey like mice and rats. It has a strong flexible body, quick reflexes, sharp teeth, and its night vision and sense of smell are well developed. It is a social species, but a solitary hunter and a crepuscular predator. Cat communication includes vocalizations like meowing, purring, trilling, hissing, growling, and grunting as well as cat body language. It can hear sounds too faint or too high in frequency for human ears, such as those made by small mammals. It also secretes and perceives pheromones.</string>
    <string name="animal_description_5">The snow leopard (Panthera uncia), commonly known as the ounce, is a species of large cat in the genus Panthera of the family Felidae. The species is native to the mountain ranges of Central and South Asia. It is listed as Vulnerable on the IUCN Red List because the global population is estimated to number fewer than 10,000 mature individuals and is expected to decline about 10% by 2040. It is mainly threatened by poaching and habitat destruction following infrastructural developments. It inhabits alpine and subalpine zones at elevations of 3,000–4,500 m (9,800–14,800 ft), ranging from eastern Afghanistan, the Himalayas and the Tibetan Plateau to southern Siberia, Mongolia and western China. In the northern part of its range, it also lives at lower elevations.</string>
    <string name="animal_description_6">The tiger (Panthera tigris) is the largest living cat species and a member of the genus Panthera. It is most recognisable for its dark vertical stripes on orange fur with a white underside. An apex predator, it primarily preys on ungulates, such as deer and wild boar. It is territorial and generally a solitary but social predator, requiring large contiguous areas of habitat to support its requirements for prey and rearing of its offspring. Tiger cubs stay with their mother for about two years and then become independent, leaving their mother\'s home range to establish their own.\nThe tiger was first scientifically described in 1758. It once ranged widely from the Eastern Anatolia Region in the west to the Amur River basin in the east, and in the south from the foothills of the Himalayas to Bali in the Sunda Islands. Since the early 20th century, tiger populations have lost at least 93% of their historic range and have been extirpated from Western and Central Asia, the islands of Java and Bali, and in large areas of Southeast and South Asia and China. What remains of the range where tigers still roam free is fragmented, stretching in spots from Siberian temperate forests to subtropical and tropical forests on the Indian subcontinent, Indochina and a single Indonesian island, Sumatra.</string>
    <string name="animal_description_7">A rhinoceros (/raɪˈnɒsərəs/; from Ancient Greek ῥῑνόκερως (rhīnókerōs) \'nose-horned\'; from ῥῑ́ς (rhī́s) \'nose\', and κέρας (kéras) \'horn\';[1] pl.: rhinoceros or rhinoceroses), commonly abbreviated to rhino, is a member of any of the five extant species (or numerous extinct species) of odd-toed ungulates in the family Rhinocerotidae; it can also refer to a member of any of the extinct species of the superfamily Rhinocerotoidea. Two of the extant species are native to Africa, and three to South and Southeast Asia.</string>
    <string name="animal_description_8">Turtles are reptiles of the order Testudines, characterized by a special shell developed mainly from their ribs. Modern turtles are divided into two major groups, the Pleurodira (side necked turtles) and Cryptodira (hidden necked turtles), which differ in the way the head retracts. There are 360 living and recently extinct species of turtles, including land-dwelling tortoises and freshwater terrapins. They are found on most continents, some islands and, in the case of sea turtles, much of the ocean. Like other amniotes (reptiles, birds, and mammals) they breathe air and do not lay eggs underwater, although many species live in or around water.</string>
    <string name="animal_description_9">Zebras (subgenus Hippotigris) are African equines with distinctive black-and-white striped coats. There are three living species: Grévy\'s zebra (Equus grevyi), the plains zebra (E. quagga), and the mountain zebra (E. zebra). Zebras share the genus Equus with horses and asses, the three groups being the only living members of the family Equidae. Zebra stripes come in different patterns, unique to each individual. Several theories have been proposed for the function of these stripes, with most evidence supporting them as a deterrent for biting flies. Zebras inhabit eastern and southern Africa and can be found in a variety of habitats such as savannahs, grasslands, woodlands, shrublands, and mountainous areas.</string>
    <string name="animal_description_10">The giraffe is a large African hoofed mammal belonging to the genus Giraffa. It is the tallest living terrestrial animal and the largest ruminant on Earth. Traditionally, giraffes were thought to be one species, Giraffa camelopardalis, with nine subspecies. Most recently, researchers proposed dividing them into up to eight extant species due to new research into their mitochondrial and nuclear DNA, as well as morphological measurements. Seven other extinct species of Giraffa are known from the fossil record.</string>

    <string name="animal_shoutout_1">Photo by <a href="https://unsplash.com/@zmachacek?utm_content=creditCopyText&amp;utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=unsplash">Zdeněk Macháček</a> on <a href="https://unsplash.com/photos/brown-lion-on-green-grass-field-UxHol6SwLyM?utm_content=creditCopyText&amp;utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=unsplash">Unsplash</a></string>
    <string name="animal_shoutout_2">Photo by <a href="https://unsplash.com/@geraninmo?utm_content=creditCopyText&amp;utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=unsplash">Geranimo</a> on <a href="https://unsplash.com/photos/brown-mammoth-on-middle-of-woods-during-daytime-f0oe9P9Yixs?utm_content=creditCopyText&amp;utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=unsplash">Unsplash</a></string>
    <string name="animal_shoutout_3">Photo by <a href="https://unsplash.com/@licole?utm_content=creditCopyText&amp;utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=unsplash">Chris Charles</a> on <a href="https://unsplash.com/photos/blue-and-green-bird-on-top-of-brown-branch-during-daytime-9APFPoNb9iw?utm_content=creditCopyText&amp;utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=unsplash">Unsplash</a></string>
    <string name="animal_shoutout_4">Photo by <a href="https://unsplash.com/@_k_arinn?utm_content=creditCopyText&amp;utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=unsplash">Karina Vorozheeva</a> on <a href="https://unsplash.com/photos/white-butterfly-resting-on-cats-nose-rW-I87aPY5Y?utm_content=creditCopyText&amp;utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=unsplash">Unsplash</a></string>
    <string name="animal_shoutout_5">Photo by <a href="https://unsplash.com/@aboeka?utm_content=creditCopyText&amp;utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=unsplash">Gwen Weustink</a> on <a href="https://unsplash.com/photos/leopard-on-tree-branch-I3C1sSXj1i8?utm_content=creditCopyText&amp;utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=unsplash">Unsplash</a></string>
    <string name="animal_shoutout_6">Photo by <a href="https://unsplash.com/@vrnex?utm_content=creditCopyText&amp;utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=unsplash">Kar Ming Moo</a> on <a href="https://unsplash.com/photos/brown-and-black-tiger-lying-on-ground-Q_3WmguWgYg?utm_content=creditCopyText&amp;utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=unsplash">Unsplash</a></string>
    <string name="animal_shoutout_7">Photo by <a href="https://unsplash.com/@redcharlie?utm_content=creditCopyText&amp;utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=unsplash">redcharlie</a> on <a href="https://unsplash.com/photos/three-rhinos-walking-on-farm-road-xtvo0ffGKlI?utm_content=creditCopyText&amp;utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=unsplash">Unsplash</a></string>
    <string name="animal_shoutout_8">Photo by <a href="https://unsplash.com/@ruizra?utm_content=creditCopyText&amp;utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=unsplash">Randall  Ruiz</a> on <a href="https://unsplash.com/photos/brown-turtle-swimming-in-ocean-LVnJlyfa7Zk?utm_content=creditCopyText&amp;utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=unsplash">Unsplash</a></string>
    <string name="animal_shoutout_9">Photo by <a href="https://unsplash.com/@sutirtab?utm_content=creditCopyText&amp;utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=unsplash">sutirta budiman</a> on <a href="https://unsplash.com/photos/group-of-zebra-walking-on-wheat-field-Jgiv1rSIpVM?utm_content=creditCopyText&amp;utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=unsplash">Unsplash</a></string>
    <string name="animal_shoutout_10">Photo by <a href="https://unsplash.com/@szubiria?utm_content=creditCopyText&amp;utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=unsplash">Sofia Zubiria</a> on <a href="https://unsplash.com/photos/giraffe-standing-on-green-grass-during-daytime-UqB0TfIdqNE?utm_content=creditCopyText&amp;utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=unsplash">Unsplash</a></string>

</resources>